











February 3, 1989 (27 old)

Ux designer and web developer, currently working as a freelancer. I am responsible for creating websites and all the necessary things that a client requests for their business to grow. In the past I worked as a web programmer and now I am more focus in ux design and front-end.

Listen, creativity, responsiveness, learning and organization are the focus of all my projects.

Work Experience

Freelancer

Lisbon, Portugal 08/2015 - Present

UX Designer & Web Developer

I am hired for investigation, design and programming websites and assisting in the creation of the brand.(business cards, email signature).

Tecnologies used:

HTML, CSS (SASS), Bootstrap, RubyOnRails, JQuery

BlackOrange

Lisbon, Portugal 05/2014 - 08/2015

Web Developer

I was responsible for participate in web developing, creating websites for clients.

Tecnologies used:

HTML, CSS (SASS), RubyOnRails, Javascript, Bootstrap, MySQL

Accenture

Lisbon, Portugal 04/2013 - 03/2014

Programmer

Working as outsourcing for Santander, responsible for requirements gathering, planning and documentation analysis(DDS), software development.

Tecnologies used:

Banksphere, a proprietary technology based on Java (J2EE) with frontend in HTML / Javascript and a language of visual components, and access to DB2 database.

Paysimplex

Lisbon, Portugal 10/2012 - 02/2013

Web Developer

Responsible for development of a system that allows private users and companies, pay the parking lot by smartphone, via SMS or PaySimplex site.

Tecnologies used:

Asp.Net, C#, HMTL5, CSS3, JavaScript

Available For

Secure a position as front-end designer.

Education

University of Lisbon

Graduate in Computer Science, in 2013

My Interests



anguages

Portuguese native English

Skills

| Coding | Design |
|-------------------|----------------|
| HTML | Prototyping |
| CSS (SASS) | Photoshop |
| RubyOnRails | Illustrator |
| Bootstrap | Sketch |
| Javascript/JQuery | Testing |
| React.JS | Human Behavior |